孩子们 我刚搬到纽约的时候\n这儿邋遢得要命 让人作呕
Kids: When I first moved to New\nYork, it was dingy, disgusting,
脏乱差不说 还跳蚤猖獗\n恶臭难闻 总之就是恐怖极了
dirty, ugly, flea-ridden,\nstinky and altogether terrifying,
可之后 遗憾的是\n整个城市突然开始走上坡路了
but then, the most awful thing happened--\nthe whole city started to go uphill.
街道干净了 房租也高了
The streets got a little cleaner,\nthe rents got a little higher,
紧接着我们喜欢的那些老地方\n也一个接一个消失了
and one by one, the crappy old\nplaces we loved began to disappear.
Elbow Room 原本是一个朋克摇滚俱乐部 \n现在变成了药店
The Elbow Room, an old punk\nrock club, became a drugstore;
McHale's 本来是家工薪阶层酒吧\n现在成了一家快餐店
McHale's, a working-class watering\nhole, became a fast-food place;
Fez 一家建于1815年的百老汇剧院\n现在也成了银行
and Fez, a Moroccan-themed\nlounge, became a bank.
并且不是家普通的银行
And not just any bank.
歌利亚国家银行
Goliath National Bank.
世界信贷银行业的领军人物
The world leader in credit and banking.
老天 我爱死歌利亚国家银行了!
God, I love Goliath National Bank!
好了 首先 \n你怎么跟中大奖了一样
Okay, first of all, you look\nlike the last pick in the draft.
其次 你干嘛对一个银行这么感兴趣?
And, uh, second, why are you\nso excited about some bank?
我们公司刚刚毫不留情地\n把他们给收购了
Our company just bought them\nout in a ruthless takeover.
花了两个月 2000个员工的饭碗丢了
Took two months. Cost 2,000 jobs.
太血淋淋了
It was brutal.
谁想要T恤?
Who wants a T-shirt?
嘿 Marshall 法律部门在招人
Hey, Marshall, they're hiring\nin the legal department.
我能帮你找份工作
I could get you a job.
Barney Marshall辞掉那份出卖灵魂的工作 \n可不是为了要到银行打工
Barney, Marshall didn't quit his last soul-sucking\ncorporate job just to go work at a bank.
他要做一名为环保事业奋斗的律师
He's gonna be an environmental lawyer.
计划的确是这样的啦
That was the plan, anyway.
那之后的几个礼拜\nMarshall参加了很多面试
Over the next few weeks, Marshall\nwent on a lot of interviews.
你有自信 有活力 有够专注!
You are confident, you are\nenergetic, you are focused!
很多面试
A lot of interviews.
你可以接受薪水的浮动 \n可以做出让步 这次你绝不会哭
You are flexible on salary, you're willing\nto compromise, you're not gonna cry this time.
非常多的面试
Too many interviews.
你真可悲 你失败了 可你会撑过去的
You are sad, you are beaten\ndown, you will get through this,
回家去 换上你的短裤衩 好好打个盹
come home, get in your big\nunderpants and take a nap.
说到这 不得不提9月29号的汉堡之夜
Which brings us to September\n29, the night of the burger.
大家想吃点啥?
So, um, what do you guys\nwant to do for dinner?
噢 我们新来了个厨子
Oh, we just got a new cook.
你们一定要试试汉堡 棒极了
You have to try the\nburger-- it's amazing.
那好吧 来五个汉堡
Oh, great-- we'll\ntake five of those.
五个汉堡
Five burgers.
等下 你确定要在这儿吃?
Whoa, um, really?\nYou-you want to eat here?
是啊 我快饿死了
Yeah, I'm freaking starving.
我刚结束了我的7日减肥疗程
I just finished a seven-day cleanse.
你不是昨天才开始吗?
I thought you just\nstarted that yesterday.
我提前结束了 不行啊
I finished early, okay?
- 五个\n- 五个汉堡
Five of those. Five burgers.
等等 要不吃寿司?
Whoa, um, wait. What about sushi?
- 哦 我们昨晚就是吃寿司\n- 意大利菜
- Oh, we had sushi last night.\n- Italian.
我中午吃的意大利餐
I had Italian for lunch.
- 我可以一会儿再来\n- 别 我们总是这样
- I can come back.\n- No. We always do this.
花上一个小时商量吃什么\n可最后还是要在这儿吃
We spend an hour arguing about where to\neat, and then we end up eating here anyway.
我两天没吃东西了
I haven't eaten for two days.
可不可以拜托大家可怜可怜我\n随便点点东西吧
Can we please, for the love of\nGod, just order something now?
中国菜?
Chinese?
我不喜欢中国菜
I don't like Chinese.
那印度菜呢?
Indian?
我说了不吃中国菜
I just said I don't like Chinese.
印度菜又不是中国菜
Indian isn't Chinese.
都是些奇怪的肉 搞笑的音乐 \n配上白米饭
Weird meats, funny music, side of rice.
分那么清楚干嘛?
Why are we splitting hairs?
墨西哥呢?
Mexican?
我说了不吃中国菜
I just said I don't like Chinese.
哦 老天爷
Oh, God.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季 第2集
How I Met\nYour Mother Season04 Episode02
1小时过后
ONE HOUR LATER
Robin 你的那份过会上
Robin, yours will be right out.
当然了 我的总是最后
Of course, mine comes last.
吃吧 不用等我了
Go ahead, start without me.
- 太好了!\n- 你真好
- Sweet!\n- That's so kind of you.
哦 我的神啊
Oh, my God.
这汉堡太棒了
This burger is so good.
好比嘴里的圣诞节--"圣肉节"
It's like Christmas in\nmy mouth-- meat Christmas.
就像跌入麦克劳伦厨房的小天使\n(MacLaren 家居厨卫用品品牌)
It's like an angel from heaven\nlanded in the kitchen at MacLaren's.
厨师用研磨机将它大卸八块
Where the chef killed it and\nran it through the meat grinder.
这个汉堡实在是太好吃了\n我都舍不得把它排泄出去...
I love this burger so much,\nI want to sew my ass shut.
还好了
It's okay.
- 你搞什么?\n- 伙计们
- Are you kidding me?\n- Guys, guys, guys.
你只要吃过纽约最好吃的汉堡 就知道世上的\n其他汉堡都只是我爷爷的干瘪脚丫而已
When you've had the best burger in New York City,\nevery other burger tastes like my grandpa's feet.
你们还是接着吃吧 \n尽情享受我爷爷的臭脚丫
But you guys eat up,\nenjoy my grandpa's feet.
哦 你吃过纽约最好的汉堡?
Oh, and you've had the\nbest burger in New York.
那是八年前了 \n我初到纽约的第一个星期
It was eight years ago,\nmy first week in New York,
对于一个从明尼苏达的乡下小伙而言 \n整个城市都有点让人毛骨悚然
and for a kid from Minnesota,\nthe big city was a scary place.
8年前
EIGHT YEARS EARLIER
谢天谢地是你
Oh, thank God it's just you.
你有点神经质了啊
You are being ridiculous.
告诉我你今天出过门了吧
Tell me you left the apartment today.
我干嘛要出去?
Why would I have to leave?
我想要啥都能送货上门 \n况且纽约的有线电视也挺好看的
I can have anything I want delivered,\nand New York City cable is awesome.
你看过讲这个穿着比基尼的犹太\n老女人的公众节目没?
Have you seen this public access show\nwith the old Jewish lady in a bikini?
实在是 太恶心了
It's, it's disgusting.
Marshall你不能再这么疑神疑鬼了
Marshall, you have to\nget over this paranoia.
你不会被打劫的
You are not gonna get mugged.
那要真被打劫了咋办呢?\n我身上友没有防身的刀片
Well, what if I do, Ted, all\nright? I don't have a switchblade.
我不知道该怎么耍霹雳\n去让帮派混混们刮目相看
I don't, I don't know how to, how to break-dance\nand win the begrudging respect of a street gang.
好了 够了够了 \n你出去转转吧 快走
All right, that's it, you're\ntaking a walk. Come on, go.
不 瞧 比基尼老女人又上场了
No. Look, the old lady\nin a bikini is back on.
- 我只想舒舒服服地躺回去\n- 快走! 快出去
- I'm just gonna lie back and get comfortable.\n- Go! Go outside, go, go.
好了
Okay.
- 球棒留下\n- 知道了!
- Leave the bat.\n- Fine.
于是我就朝着这个可怕的\n大都市走了过去
So I went for a walk\nin the big, scary city.
并且发现了一件事 其实一点也不可怕
And I discovered something\namazing: it wasn't scary at all.
你好吗
All right.
什么来着?
What's the word?
你终于找到了你想要的!
Your search is over!
之后 正当我觉得有点饿的时候\n我来到了一个拐角...
And then, right when I started to get\na little hungry, I turned a corner...
就在那儿
and there it was.
那是我所见过最小的汉堡小店
The tiniest little\nburger joint you ever saw,
夹在一家标本店跟\n一家某某某书店中间
tucked between a taxidermist\nand a triple-X bookstore.
两个东西上架的地方\n(get stuffed 也有滚开之意)
Name two places where\nthings get stuffed.
于是 我就进去了
So, I went inside.
点了一个汉堡
And I ordered the burger.
谢谢
Thank you.
Ted  Ted 快醒醒 Ted 快醒...
Ted. Ted, you got to\nwake up. Ted, wake...
哦 上帝 对不起 你没事儿吧?
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry. Are you okay?
没事
I'm all right.
Ted  Ted 我刚吃了这辈子最好吃的汉堡!
Ted. Ted, I've just had the\nmost amazing burger of my life!
一个很棒的小地方 Regis Philbin在那吃过\n(脱口秀主持人)
It's this awesome little\nplace, Regis Philbin eats there,
所以也是个名人场所
so it's sort of like\na celebrity hot spot.
不过关键是汉堡 Ted 汉堡
But the burger, Ted. The burger.
老兄 我现在就想来个那里的汉堡!
Dude. I want one of\nthose burgers right now!
现在关门没?
Do you think they're still open?
不知道 纽约的店子\n九点半钟之后关门吗?
I don't know. Does stuff in\nNew York stay open past... 9:30?
于是我们想再出去买汉堡
So we went out to get another burger.
可是找了好几个小时...
But after hours of searching...
见鬼! 上哪儿去了?
Damn it! Where is this place?
找不到了吗?
You couldn't find it?
我们完全弄不清方向了
We didn't know our way around.
我们花了三个小时才回家\n还是多亏了那个男扮女装的家伙
Just getting back to the apartment took us\nthree hours and one very helpful drag queen.
等等 Betty Noir是男扮女装的?
Wait, Betty Noir was a drag queen?
那你们觉得它上哪儿去了?
Well, where do you think it was?
也许在她两腿之间吧
Probably tucked between her legs.
知道什么不忽悠吗?\n(drag queen中drag也有忽悠之意)
You know what's not a drag?
到歌利亚国家银行\n办一份家庭资产贷款吧
Getting a home equity loan\nat Goliath National Bank.
随便说说
I'm just saying.
总之 我们是再也没有找到过那个地方
Anyways, um, we never found the place.
如今 8年过去了 还是...
Now, eight years have passed, still...
吃不上像样的汉堡
no burger.
我不是有意听你们谈话的
I couldn't help but overhear.
好吧... 又来了
Okay, here we go.
我知道你们说的地方
I know the place you're talking about.
不 你不知道
No, you don't.
那地方叫Corner Bistro
It's a place called the Corner Bistro.
最好的汉堡
Great burger.
哦 原来是Corner Bistro啊!
Oh, the Corner Bistro!
太奇妙了 我花了人生的四分之一时间\n在纽约城里寻找最好的汉堡
It's amazing, I spent a quarter of my life\nsearching for the best burger in New York City,
我真是笨呐 怎么没想到去\nZagat咨询里查查排名最高的汉堡是啥
but silly me, it never occurred to me to check\nthe highest-rated burger in the Zagat guide.
真是多谢你了 伙计
Wow, thanks a lot, guy.
那我也来帮你个忙吧
Let me return the favor.
最好的咖啡是星巴克
Um, great cup of coffee: Starbucks.
那你就是试过Corner Bistro咯
So I take it you've\ntried the Corner Bistro.
Robin 为了找到那个汉堡...\n又或者是忘掉她...
Robin, I've tried every so-called best burger\nin New York City trying to find that burger.
我去过城里每家自诩拥有\n最好汉堡的店
Or at least forget about her.
Corner Bistro\nCORNER BISTRO
Paul's Place\nPAUL'S PLACE
"21"\n"21"
Veggie Heaven\nVEGGIE HEAVEN
我们走吧
We're going.
都没一家沾上边的
But none of those\nplaces even came close.
嘿 有一次我们以为我们终于可以有突破了 \n还记得吗?
Hey, there was that one time we thought\nwe had a break in the case, remember?
听好了
Get this.
你知道我在健身房看见谁了吗?
You know who works out at my gym?
Regis Philbin\nRegis Philbin.
(在汉堡店)留签名的家伙
The autographed picture.
我当然记得那地方啦
Of course I remember the place.
那是我吃过最好的汉堡
It was the best burger I ever had.
我到现在还常做那个汉堡的梦呢
I still have dreams about this burger.
魂牵梦萦啊!
Beautiful, haunting dreams!
夜里我经常会说着这样的梦话醒来\n"滚出去 汉堡!给我滚出去!"
I wake up at night screaming, "Get\nout of my head, burger! Get out!"
就是那个 Philbin先生
That's the one, Mr. Philbin.
记得在哪儿吗?
Do you remember where it is?
不记得了!我没写下来
No! I never wrote it down.
自那过后我没有一天不在后悔的
But not a day goes by\nthat I don't regret it.
怎么了? 你知道在哪儿吗?
Why? Why? Do you know where it is?
如果你告诉我是Corner Bistro的话\n小心我打你!
And if you tell me it's at the Corner\nBistro, I'm gonna smack you right in the face!
不 我们不知道在哪儿
No, we don't, we don't know where it is.
听着 小黄毛! 别给我添乱!
Listen, Blondie! Don't mess with me!
爹地要吃那汉堡!
Daddy needs his meat.
我真不知道在哪儿 Regis 我发誓!
I don't know where\nit is, Regis, I swear!
你呢 衰仔?
What about you, Lurch?
你呢 小包嘴?
And what about you, satchel-mouth?
这是我电话
This is my cell.
找到汉堡立刻通知我 不管什么时候
You find that burger,\nyou call me day or night.
好的 Regis 一定 一定
Okay, Regis, we will, we will.
好了 你们还干站着干嘛?\n还不快去找汉堡!
All right, so what are you waiting\nfor? Get out and find the burger!
- 好的 好的\n- 快去!
- All right, all right.\n- Let's go, all of you!
故事就这么告一段落了
That's where my story ends.
我想即使我走遍全世界\n也找不到那扇小绿门
Now I'm doomed to walk the earth\nforever searching for that green door
看不见那个写着"汉堡"的红色\n霓虹招牌了
and that red neon sign\nthat says "Burger."
绿门 写着"汉堡"的红色霓虹招牌?
Green door, red neon\nsign that says "Burger?"
- 是啊\n- 我知道那地方
- Yeah.\n- I know that place.
那地方我经过无数次了\n在西12大道 7大道往右拐
I've walked by it a million times.\nIt's on West 12th, right off of 7th.
我就知道在一条带数字的街上!
I knew it was on a numbered street!
- 终于来了\n- 不! Robin!
- Finally.\n- No! Robin!
今天晚上要吃汉堡\n也得吃全纽约最好的
If any of us is gonna eat a burger tonight,\nit's gonna be the best burger in New York.
- 我们进城去!\n- 不...
- We're going downtown!\n- No...
难以置信我们终于能吃上那汉堡了
believe we're finally\ngonna have this burger.
宝贝 我太为你高兴了
Honey, I'm so excited for you.
经历了这么多面试 这么多失望
After all these interviews,\nafter all these disappointments,
你是该好好地吃上一口
you deserve a triumphant\nmouth full of meat.
知道还有什么是一口嘛?\n(这里指嗦)
You know what else is a mouthful?
其他银行对你的含糊其辞满嘴胡言
All that double-talk\nother banks give you.
而在歌利亚 顾客的满意\n是我们最重要的投资
At Goliath, customer satisfaction\nis our most important investment.
Barney 我不想打击你 \n但在银行工作有点逊
Barney, I hate to break this to you,\nbut working for a bank's kind of lame.
可不是嘛
Oh, yeah.
免费自动付账单逊不逊 Lil?
How lame is free\nautomatic bill pay, Lil?
网上存款年收益3.3%逊不逊?
How lame is 3. 3% APY online savings?
是的 没有错
Yeah! That's right.
抱歉让你在朋友面前颜面尽失 \n但这是你逼我的
Hate to make you look stupid in front of\nyour friends, but you left me no choice.
我们该打给Regis
we should probably call Regis.
Reg... 我怕这家伙
Reg... Oh, that guy scares me.
我想还是发短信好了
I think I'll leave him a text.
Kathy 刚才一掷是人头那面
Now, Kathy, your last flip was heads.
再之前那次是字那面
The one before that was tails.
你求助观众\n他们的选择是一半一半
You polled the audience,\nthey came out split, 50/50.
完全帮不到你
No help at all there.
为了25万8千元的奖金...
So, for $258,000...
我要问你 Kathy 你要选哪个 \n人头还是...
I have to ask you, Kathy, what's\nit gonna be: heads... or...
抱歉 老天 我得走了 得赶紧走
Excuse me. Oh, boy. I-I've\ngot to go. I've got to go!
绿色大门 红色霓虹灯标志 \n伙计们 就是这地方
Green door, red neon sign.\nGuys, this is the place.
不 其实呢 我准备说几句话
Oh, n-no, I've actually, I've\nactually, um, I prepared a few words.
我饿到要吃你的手了
I will eat your hand.
这样啊 那进去好了
All right, well, let's just\ngo inside then. Shall we?
- 谢谢\n- 不客气
- Thank you.\n- You're welcome.
你的那份请稍等
Yours will be right out.
得了 你们吃吧 开动吧
Please, go ahead, start.
哎呀 这样...
Oh, no...
- 闭嘴赶快吃\n- 好吧
- Just shut up and eat.\n- All right.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我再也不刷牙了 \n除非牙刷也是用这汉堡做的
I'm never brushing my teeth again unless\nit's with a toothbrush made from this burger.
我想我刚经历了人生中的第一次汉堡高潮
I think I just had my first burg-asm.
我想...
I want...
把这汉堡带出去 然后一起看个电影 \n再带回我家
to take this burger out to dinner, then\nmaybe a movie, then take it back to my place,
然后放点Terence Trent D'arby的音乐 之后我就...
put on a little Terence Trent\nD'arby, and then I would just...
稍稍乱搞一下关系
fool around a little bit.
随便玩玩...放慢脚步 明白不
Nothing serious-- just\ntake it slow, you know?
- 不是这个\n- 什么?
- This isn't it.\n- What?
真的不是
It's not it.
Marshall 也许你不想听我说这些...
Okay, Marshall, you might\nnot want to hear this, but...
有没有可能这就是你八年前\n吃的同样的汉堡
is it at all possible this is the\nsame burger you had eight years ago,
只是你的期望过高 \n所以变得有些无理取闹呢
only it could never live up to\nyour ridiculously high expectations?
我觉得不过是个汉堡
I mean, it is just a burger.
不过是个汉堡? 不过是个汉堡?
Just a burger? Just a burger?
Robin 这可不仅仅是个汉堡
Robin, it's so much\nmore than just a burger.
咬下第一口... 感觉置身于天堂
I, I mean, that first bite-- oh,\nwhat heaven that first bite is.
汉堡胚宛若洒满芝麻粒的天使乳房
The bun, like a sesame\n- freckled breast of an angel,
下面静静的安放着番茄酱和芥末
resting gently on the\nketchup and mustard below.
味道混合而成一场极具诱惑力的双人舞蹈
Flavors mingling in a\nseductive pas de deux.
然后...
And then...
是酸黄瓜 最具趣味的小小酸黄瓜 \n然后是一片番茄
a pickle-- the most playful little\npickle, and then a slice of tomato,
再加一片生菜 \n以及细腻精致的一片牛肉饼
a leaf of lettuce, and a, a patty\nof ground beef so exquisite...
味道在你的嘴里打转 分开又融合
swirling in your mouth, breaking\napart and combining again
味道如此甜美可口...
in a fugue of sweets and savories so...
令人心旷神怡
delightful.
这绝不仅仅是烤肉三明治和吐司面包 Robin
This is no mere sandwich of grilled\nmeat and toasted bread, Robin.
这是上帝通过食物与我们进行的对话
This is God speaking to us through food.
你既然这么有才 当初还从网上下结婚宣言
And you got our wedding\nvows off the Internet.
好吧 不是这里
Okay, uh, look, so, so\nthis, this isn't the place.
行了 也没什么大不了
All right, it's no big deal.
是另一个绿色大门 红色霓虹灯\n写着"汉堡"的地方而已
It's another place with a green door\nand a red neon sign that says "Burger."
我会给曼哈顿每间餐馆打电话 \n问清大门的颜色
I'll just, uh, I'll call every restaurant in\nManhattan and ask 'em what color their door is.
小事一桩 对吧 就这么做吧
No big deal, right? Let's do this.
我也要出去独自嚷嚷这不仅仅是个汉堡
I'm going to go out on a limb here\nand say this isn't just about a burger.
Marshall最近不太好 伙计们
Marshall's not doing so well, guys.
他真的需要工作了
He really needs to get a job.
跟他们说说内裤的事
Tell them about the underpants.
啥内裤的事?
What about the underpants?
事情开始于几周前
It started a couple of weeks ago.
人头! 肯定是人头面!
Heads! It's going to be heads.
总是人头的嘛
It's almost usually heads.
嘿 宝贝
Hey, baby.
你今天穿过裤子了没
Did you put on pants today?
没
Nope.
起初还挺有趣 但后来几乎成了日常惯例
It was funny at first, but\nthen it became a daily thing.
我想"至少他没穿这样出门去"
I thought, "Okay, well, at least\nhe's not leaving the house like that."
之后 有天他直接打开门去拿报纸
Then, one day, he opened\nthe door to get the paper.
再后来 走到楼下去拿信
Day after that, went\ndownstairs to get the mail.
每个人都有自己的内裤半径
Everyone's got an underpants radius.
我们大部分人的范围仅限于\n从卧室到卫生间
For most of us, it's the distance\nfrom the bedroom to the bathroom,
随着羞耻心的减小 内裤半径会越来越大
but as your self\n- esteem gets smaller, your underpants radius gets bigger.
那Marshall的内裤半径究竟多大?
How big is Marshall's underpants radius?
我们走吧
We're going.
好了 Lily 他总有天会找到工作的
Come on, Lily, he'll\nfind a job eventually.
知道吗Lil 当世事险恶时 \n我会记起那首我最爱的歌曲
You know, Lil, when times are tough, I like to\nremember the uplifting words of my favorite song.
* 当你需要朋友 我们常伴你左右 *
* We'll be on your side\nwhen you need a friend *
* 不顾任何困难险阻 *
* Through thick and thin *
* 可以一直让你依靠 *
* You can always depend *
* 世界贷款和银行业的典范 *
* On the world leaders\nIn credit and banking...*
* 歌利亚国家银行 *
* Goliath National Bank.*
联邦储蓄保险公司会员哦
Member FDIC.
我们得帮Marshall找到那个汉堡
We've got to find Marshall that burger.
Lily 我想我们已经吃到了
Lily, I think we're\nall eating that burger.
我可没吃
I'm not eating that burger.
不 如果Marshall说不是 那就不是
No, if Marshall says this isn't\nthe burger, this isn't the burger.
总算来了
Finally.
- 不好意思\n- 什么事
- Excuse me.\n- Yes.
你们是不是换厨师了或者什么的
Did you guys change cooks or something?
因为我丈夫肯定几年前\n来这里吃的味道不同
Because my husband was here five years ago,\nand he's pretty sure he had a different burger.
我们经常碰到这事
Yeah, we get this a lot.
这个店是按照住宅区的另一间店建的 \n也是绿色大门和"汉堡"标志
This place is modeled after this other place\nuptown with the same green door and "Burger" sign.
啥? 住宅区? 在哪
What? Uptown? Where?
曼哈顿区106大道
106th and Manhattan Avenue.
真该死
Damn it.
106大道 数字街道 没错
106 A numbered street. Of course.
我是Barney Stinson
Barney Stinson.
Barney 你死哪去了?
Barney, where the hell are you?
不好意思 请问你是...
I'm sorry, this is...
Regis 我到那边了
Regis. I'm at the place.
Regis 可不是嘛
Oh, Regis, of course.
对不起 对不起 我忘记打给你了
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm\nsorry. I forgot to call you.
不是那个地方
That's not the place.
真正的地方是在曼哈顿区106大道上
The real place is on\n106th and Manhattan Avenue.
我们已经开车去那了
We're headed there right now.
啥 住宅区?
What? Uptown?
好吧好吧 我20分钟后到
Fine, fine, I'll be there in 20.
如果你先到那里 给我来个半生半熟的
If you get there first, medium rare.
- 加洋葱吗?\n- 加洋葱?
- Onions?\n- Onions?
好吧 不加
Okay, no onions.
快停车!
Stop the cab!
等下 就是这里
Wait. This is it.
你已经找到你想要的了!
Your search is over.
- 这里有脱衣女孩\n- 就是这里
- We got girls taking off their clothes.\n- This is it.
9千个的方便网点
One of 9,000 convenient locations.
就是在这里的
It was, it was right on this very spot.
我想不通 卖汉堡的地方去了哪
I don't understand.\nWhere is the burger place?
这里不再是汉堡店了 变成了\n歌利亚国家银行提款机
It's not a burger place anymore;\nit's a... Goliath National Bank ATM.
挺好 我们就在这里吃吧
W-Well, that's fine.\nLet's just eat here.
不能在这里吃 这是提款机
We can't eat here. It's an ATM.
但也有能吃的东西
But food.
嘿 你要干吗...
Ow, ow, hey,\nwhat the--?
全是你的错 你和你的白痴银行
This is your fault, you\nand your stupid bank.
- 全是你一手造成的\n- 不怪我...行了
- You did this. - It's\nnot my-- stop, okay.
住手吧 Lily
Stop that, Lily.
我绝对不会用歌利亚提款机
I will never use a\nGoliath ATM ever again.
歌利亚国家银行糟透了
Goliath National Bank sucks.
是地球上最烂的银行
It's the worst bank on\nthe face of the earth.
大家听着 纽约人 \n这家银行逊啊 太逊了
Attention, New Yorkers,\nthis bank sucks! They suck!
- 天啊 Marshall 你干嘛不告诉她?\n- 逊透了 烂毙了
- Aw, geez.Marshall, will you just tell her already?\n- They suck, suck, suck!
告诉我啥
Tell me what?
我找到工作了
I got a job.
什么 在哪
What? Where?
在歌利亚国家银行
Goliath National Bank.
所以Barney才一直说那些 说歌利亚有多好
That's why Barney's been going on and\non about how, how great Goliath is.
他希望你替我感到高兴 \n我们要一起工作了
He wanted you to be excited for me since\nwe're going to be working there together.
技术上来讲不算一起
Well, technically not together.
你可没有资格到我的那层楼
You won't have access to my floor.
但你想做的是一名环境律师
But you want to be an\nenvironmental lawyer.
我还想加入哈林篮球组织换糖吃呢 但...
Yeah, you know, and I also want to be a Harlem\nGlobetrotter and get paid in candy, but...
与此同时 我需要工作 这的确是好工作
in the meantime, I need a job, and\nthis is, this is a really good one.
高薪高福利 而且老实讲
It's great pay and there's\ngood benefits, and to be honest,
这也让我有理由在早上穿上裤子
it gives me a reason to\nput on pants in the morning.
我有一生的时间来拯救地球 但此时此刻
You know, I have my whole life to\nsave the planet, but right now I'm,
我真的有些期待再次穿上裤子的感觉了
I'm kind of really excited\nto wear pants again.
你的裤子很好看的
You've got great pants.
- 我爱你\n- 我也爱你
- I love you.\n- I love you.
Robin 别这样
Robin, no.
- 还没打开过的
- Give it.\n- They're unopened.\n- Give it.
- 烤肉味的\n- 拿过来
- They're barbecue.\n- Give it!
抱歉你没能吃到汉堡
I'm sorry you didn't get your burger.
这想法很傻 我想到了来纽约的第一周
It's stupid. I think about that\nfirst week in New York. You know?
我当时22岁
I was 22 years old.
我有光明的前途
I had my whole future ahead of me.
我只是觉得如果我能再吃一次汉堡
I guess I just kind of thought that if\nI could have that burger one more time
再感受下那晚的感觉 我也许能告别过去
and feel that way for one more night, that\nI might be able to check that off the list,
成长起来 去那间蠢银行上班 \n开开心心每一天
and grow up, go work for the\nstupid bank, and just be happy.
知道吗 汉堡店还在
You know, that burger place isn't gone.
只是搬了个地方
It just moved to a new location.
我可以告诉你们在那里 但要给我100块
And I can tell you where\nthat is for a hundred bucks.
100块? 简直是疯了
A hundred bucks? That's crazy.
我们掏钱吧
Let's pay the man.
- 我的钱付出租车了\n- 我没带现金
- I paid for the cab.\n- I don't have any cash.
我从三月起就失业了
I haven't worked since March.
有一种既简单又方便的方法\n来立刻提取现金
Wow, if only there were an easy,\nconvenient way to get some cash right now.
联邦储蓄保险公司会员哦
Member FDIC.
然后我们付了钱 20分钟后...
So we paid the guy,\nand 20 minutes later...
好了 Marshall 记住此刻
All right, Marshall, remember.
也许味道不如当初
It might not taste as good.
地方变了 你也变了 整个纽约都变了
This place has changed, you've\nchanged, New York has changed.
别抱太大希望 好吗
Just... don't get your\nhopes up too high, okay?
- 就是这个味\n- 好耶
- This is it.\n- Yes!
一模一样的味道
It's exactly the same.
这是纽约最棒的汉堡
It's the best burger in New York.
继续 吃吧 吃吧
Go ahead, eat up, eat up.
所以 在终于再次品尝过他\n这么些年朝思暮想的汉堡后
And so, after finally tasting again the\nburger he'd craved for so many years,
Marshall第二天早上起床 \n穿上裤子便去上班 再也没有往回看
Marshall got up the next morning, put on some\npants, and went to work, and he never looked back.
我真想用这汉堡铺成床
I want to get tiny fitted\nsheets for this burger,
滚在汉堡胚上 温温软软的死在这上面
and just crawl into this bun,\nget all cozy, and die there.
老天 我真想你填满我
Oh, my God. I just\nwant you inside of me.
真是好吃啊
This feels so good.
真担心我会让这个汉堡怀孕
I'm worried I'm gonna\nget this burger pregnant.
如果他真能让汉堡怀孕 \n我也有权索要汉堡的宝宝
If he does get that burger pregnant, I\nhave dibs on the delicious burger babies.
- 不是这个味道\n- 啥?
- This isn't it.\n- What?
不 Regis Philbin 少来
No, Regis Philbin. Come on.
这太气人了 简直难以置信
That's outrageous. That is unbelievable.
等下 就是这个味!
Wait. This is it, yes!
你真是吓了我们一大跳 Philbin
You were just freakin'\nteasing us, Philbin.